Guide to the Edward H. Knight, Class of 1898, Yale College, Photograph Collection Documenting Student Life at Yale and in New Haven
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Edward H. Knight, Class of 1898, Yale College, photograph collection documenting student life at Yale and in New Haven
1898-1898
RU 646
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.75
The materials consist of photographs of Edward H. Knight (Yale 1898) depicting Yale buildings, student life, sports on Old Campus, and scenes of New Haven, Connecticut.
Knight, Edward Hussey, 1877-1974
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 48-A (YRG 48-A), Yale pictorial records and collections.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
Arranged by subject.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of photographs of Edward H. Knight (Yale 1898) depicting Yale buildings, student life, sports on Old Campus, and scenes of New Haven, Connecticut.
New Haven (Conn.) -- Pictorial works; Photographs; Knight, Edward Hussey, 1877-1974; Yale University -- Pictorial works; Yale University -- Buildings; Yale University -- Sports; Yale University -- Students
- Photographs, Series I
  - Yale buildings, circa 1898 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Yale rooms, circa 1898 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Yale friends, circa 1898 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Sports: crew, football, baseball, track, circa 1898 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - New Haven, circa 1898 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - East and West Rock, New Haven, circa 1898 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Lake Saltonstall, circa 1898 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Light House Point, circa 1898 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Mount Carmel -Sleeping Giant, circa 1898 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - New London and Ocean Beach, circa 1898 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - New York, circa 1898 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - West Haven and Savin Rock, circa 1898 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous, circa 1898 (Box 2, Folder 13)